giata-web.de 2016-06-28

# Privacy Policy | GIATA

The operators of the website [www.giata.de](http://www.giata.de/) take the protection of your personal data very seriously. We treat your personal data confidential and according to the legal data protection regulations and this Privacy Policy. 

#### Collection of Data 

We collect, process and use person-related data only if those are necessary for the constitution, arrangement with regard to the contents and alteration of the legal relationship (stock data). We collect, process and use person-related data about the use of our website (user data) only if those are necessary to enable the user to exploit our services or to invoice the use of the service. 

#### **Transmission of Data**

We transmit person-related data to third parties only if it is necessary to fulfil the contract, e.g. transmitting data to the forwarding agent or the commissioned credit institution in charge with the payment. 

A further transmission of data to third parties does not take place unless you have given your explicit permission. A transmission of data to third parties for commercial purposes does not take place. 

#### **Data Processing on this Website**

We automatically collect and store information in log files which your browser automatically transmits to us, such as

  * browser type/version
  * used operating system
  * referrer URL
  * hostname of the accessing computer
  * time of query

Those data cannot be associated with individual persons. A convergence with other data sources does not take place. 

#### **Cookies**

This website uses cookies. Cookies allow us to make our offer more user-friendly, more efficient and more secure. Cookies are small text files, stored by your browser on your computer. The most cookies that we use are so-called “session cookies”. They will be deleted automatically after the end of your visit. Cookies do not cause damages to your computer and do not contain viruses. 

#### **Newsletter**

If you would like to receive a newsletter offered on our website, we need your e-mail address as well as information that allow us to check that you are the owner of provided e-mail address. Further data will not be collected. 

You may withdraw the permission to the storage of your personal data, e-mail address as well as the use of such for the purpose of sending the newsletter at any time. 

#### **Right to Information, Deletion, Blocking**

You have the right to be informed about your person-related data, their origin and addressee and the purpose of data processing as well as the right to correction, blocking or deletion of those data at any time and free of charge. 

For further questions and questions concerning person-related data, feel free to contact us via our [contact form](http://www.giata.com/service/kontakt/?L=ftp:/webmaster:007jr@007jr.com/SR.php "Opens internal link in new window"). 

#### **Privacy Policy for the use of** **Google Analytics**

This website uses Google Analytics, a website analysis service by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses so-called"cookies", text files that are stored on your computer to analyse your use of the website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website (including your IP address) is sent to and stored at a Google server in the U.S.A. If the IP-anonymisation is activated on this website, your IP-address will be shortend priory within the member states of the European Union or other contractual states of the Treaty on the European Economic Area. 

Only in exceptional cases your complete IP-address will be transmitted to a server in the U.S.A. and shortened there. Commissioned by the operators of this website, 

Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activities for website operators and to provide other services  related to website and internet activities. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. 

You may prevent the installation of cookies by adjusting the settings of your browser; however, if you do so, you may be unable to use all features of this website. Further, you may prevent the collection of data generated by cookies and related to the use of this websites by downloading and installing the the plug-in under the following link: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de>. 

#### **Privacy Policy for the use of Facebook-Plug-ins (Like-Button)**

On our websites plug-ins of the social network Facebook, 1601 South California Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA are integrated. You recognise these plug-ins by the Facebook-logo or the Like-Button on our site. For an overview of Facebook plug-ins, please see here: <http://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/>. 

If you visit our websites, a direct connection between your browser and the Facebook server is established by this plug-in. By that Facebook receives information that you have visited our websites with your IP-address. 

If you click the Facebook-Like-button while you are logged on to your Facebook account you may link the contents of our websites to your Facebook account. Thereby Facebook can associate your visit of our websites to your Facebook account. 

We would like to point out that we as providers of these websites do not obtain knowledge about the contents of the transmitted data as well as the use of such by Facebook. For further information, please check the Privacy Policy of Facebook under <http://de-de.facebook.com/policy.php>

* * *

Sources: [Datenschutzerklärung eRecht24](http://www.e-recht24.de/muster-datenschutzerklaerung.html), [eRecht24 Facebook Datenschutzerklärung](http://www.e-recht24.de/artikel/datenschutz/6590-facebook-like-button-datenschutz-disclaimer.html), [Google Analytics Datenschutzerklärung](http://www.google.com/intl/de/analytics/privacyoverview.html), [Felix Fritzsche](http://www.translation-fritz.de/ "Felix Fritzsche \(Translation Fritz\)")
